viralandroid.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy | Viral Android – Tutorials, Examples, UX/UI Design

Last Edited on 2016-02-02

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

**What and when we collect personal information from the people that visit our blog?**

We do not collect information from visitors of our site until you enter your information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when subscribe our newsletter, contact us from our contact form and comment on our site.

**How do we protect visitor information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.  
We do not use Malware Scanning.  
We do not use an SSL certificate  
      • We only provide articles and information, we never ask for personal or private information like phone numbers, or credit card numbers.

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

We do not use cookies for tracking purposes.

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en  
We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.  
We do not collect personal information

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

**Fair Information Practices**

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify the users via in site notification  
      • Within 7 business days

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, follow the instruction at the bottom of each email.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using our [contact form](http://www.viralandroid.com/p/contact-us.html).
